# LOUVELLE MORRIS

# SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

## CONTACT

CELL: 0768364904

EMAIL; louvellemorris@gmail.com

LINKEDIN:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/louvelle-

morris-120112212/

GITHUB:

https://github.com/LoneWolfLou

### EDUCATION

#### EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION

Hyperion Dev

7 February

2022 - 28

August 2022

# EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION

Umbilo Secondary

2002 - 2006

## SKILLS

JAVA

Python

**SQL** 

Mysql

machine learning

HTLML

CSS

Javascript

Nodejs

Flask

React

## SUMMARY

Hard working, prompt, diligent individual who has more than 14 years work experience in a variety of fields and environments. Team player & adaptable working on my own. The goal is to become a senior developer as i am passionate about all things programming.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### BOOKKEEPER

Forbay Consulting

02 May 2013 - 12 May 2021

- Office clerk
- Bookkeeping.
- Administration.
- Data capturing
- Reason for leaving unethical work practices

## ASSISTANT SUPERVISOR/SALES FLOOR ASSISTANT/ CASHIER ADMINISTRATION

Woolworths

# 14 September 2009 - 30 April 2013

- Receiving of truck ticketing.
- Labelling of goods.
- Stock take.
- Floor planning.
- Reason for Leaving: Received an opportunity from Forbay Consulting.

#### EARLIER WORK EXPERIENCES

## Ask on request